http://www.johnheilbrun.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAbout the FirmCincinnati Family LawyerDivorce/Dissolution ConsultationFamily LawDivorceQuestions about DivorceLegal SeparationDivorce LawsCincinnati Property Division AttorneyAnnulment vs. DivorceDivorce PlanningHow to Choose a Divorce AttorneyChild Custody and Child SupportChild CustodyChild SupportDefining Best Interests of the Child in Cincinnati Divorce CasesCommon Questions about Child CustodyCollaborative DivorceDivorce MediationDissolution of MarriageDissolution vs. DivorceAlimony and Spousal SupportQualifying for Alimony/Spousal SupportCommon Questions about Spousal SupportPost-Decree ProblemsBlogFAQContact UsThis privacy policy applies to information collected online
from users of this website. In this policy, you can learn what kind of
information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we
protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to your personal
information.What personal information is collected through this website
and how is it used?We collect information
about our users in three ways: directly
from the user, from our Web server logs and through cookies. We use the
information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience
that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant
and helpful to you. We don’t share any of the information you provide with
others, unless we say so in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good
faith that the law requires it.User-supplied information: If you fill out the contact form on this
website, we will ask you to provide some personal information (such as e-mail
address, name, phone number and state). We only require that you provide an e-mail address on the contact form. Further,
if chat is available through this site, you may be asked to provide information
if you participate in an online chat. Please do not submit any confidential,
proprietary or sensitive personally identifiable information (e.g. Social
Security Number; date of birth; drivers license number; or credit card, bank
account or other financial information) (collectively, “Sensitive
Information”). If you submit any Sensitive Information, you do so at your own
risk and we will not be liable to you or responsible for consequences of your
submission.Information that you
provide to us through the contact form or an online chat will be used so that we
may respond to your inquiry. We may also use information you provide to us to
communicate with you in the future. If you do not wish to receive such
communications, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described below.Web server logs: When you visit our
website, we may track information about your visit and store that information
in web server logs, which are records of the activities on our sites. The servers
automatically capture and save the information electronically. Examples of the
information we may collect include:your unique Internet protocol address;the name of your unique Internet service provider;the town/city, county/state and country from which you access our website;the kind of browser or computer you use;the number of links you click within the site;the date and time of your visit;the web page from which you arrived to our site;the pages you viewed on the site; andcertain searches/queries that you conducted via our website(s).The
information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the site, analyze
its usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use and
improve the user’s experience.Cookies: In order to offer and
provide a customized and personal service, our websites and applications may
use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply
small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored
on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and
to help you navigate our sites during your visits. Cookies allow us to save
passwords and preferences for you so you won’t have to re-enter them each time
you visit.The
use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to
accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify
you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should
understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you
don’t accept cookies.How is personal information protected?We take certain appropriate
security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental
loss and from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, we cannot
guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security
measures.Who has access to the information?We
will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user data to others, and
we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated
parties, except as follows:to agents, website vendors and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us;if we are unable to assist with your matter, but know an unaffiliated attorney or firm that may be able to help you, we may refer you and share information you provided us with that party; andas required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.How can I correct, amend or
delete my personal information and/or opt out of future communications?You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any
time. Contact us via the phone number,
contact form or mailing address on our website at any time to:see what data we have about you, if any;change/correct any data we have about you;ask us to delete any data we have about you; and/oropt out of future communications from us.If you have any additional questions or concerns about this
privacy policy, please contact us via the phone number, contact form or mailing
address listed on this website. If our information practices change in a
significant way, we will post the policy changes here.Family Law ServicesCollaborative DivorceDivorce MediationDissolution/Divorce ConsultationFollow Us
Call |
(513) 321-3940
I have read the disclaimer.DisclaimerThe information you obtain at this site is not, nor is it intended to be, legal advice. You should consult an attorney for advice regarding your individual situation. Contacting us does not create an attorney-client relationship. Please do not send any confidential information to us until such time as an attorney-client relationship has been established. Close LinkWhat is bigger, 5 or 9? * Required Fields
